https://www.redalkemi.com/page/privacy-policy

Toggle navigation Menu
Our ServicesBranding & DesignWeb PresenceWeb MaintenanceOur WorkLogo & StationeryBrand Guides & AssetsMarketing CollateralWebsite DesignLanding PagesUI/UX DesignCase StudiesOur StoryTeamClientsTestimonialsBlogContact Us
Privacy Policy
What are cookies?
Cookies are simple text files that are stored on your computer or mobile device by a website’s server. Each cookie is unique to your web browser. It will contain some anonymous information such as a unique identifier, website’s domain name, and some digits and numbers.
What types of cookies do we use?
Necessary cookies
Necessary cookies allow us to offer you the best possible experience when accessing and navigating through our website and using its features. For example, these cookies let us recognize that you have created an account and have logged into that account to access the content.
Functionality cookies
Functionality cookies let us operate the site in accordance with the choices you make. For example, we will recognize your username and remember how you customized the site during future visits.
Analytical cookies
These cookies enable us and third-party services to collect aggregated data for statistical purposes on how our visitors use the website. These cookies do not contain personal information such as names and email addresses and are used to help us improve your user experience of the website.
We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
How to delete cookies?
If you want to restrict or block the cookies that are set by our website, you can do so through your browser setting. Alternatively, you can visit www.internetcookies.org, which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of browsers and devices. You will find general information about cookies and details on how to delete cookies from your device.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this cookie policy or our use of cookies, please contact us
This site is owned by RedAlkemi Online Private Limited. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information that you may provide via this site. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information to this site.
Consent
By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Information Collected and subscriptions
In general, you can visit this Website without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself.
RedAlkemi may, if you so choose send subscriptions to you at the address given by you. You have the option to 'opt-out' of this subscription by way of links provided on Website. We respect your privacy and in the event that you choose to not receive such subscriptions, we will take all steps to remove you from the list.
Use and Disclosure
Except as otherwise stated, we may use information collected via this site to improve the content of our site, to customize the site to your preferences, to communicate information to you (if you have requested it), and for any other purpose specified.
It is to clarify that RedAlkemi Online Private Limited never issues communication (E-mail, SMS or call) asking for bank account details from any consumer. RedAlkemi Online Private Limited appeals to members of public not to respond to such mails, SMS or calls and not to share their bank account details with anyone claiming to be from RedAlkemi.
Changes
RedAlkemi Online Private Limited reserves every right to add, modify or delete portions of the privacy policy at any time without prior notice. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information. This privacy policy was last updated on March 05, 2018.
Privacy PolicySitemapWrite a Guest PostJoin the TeamRedAlkemi White Label PartnershipContact Us
Subscribe to Our Newsletter!
© Worldwide Copyright Reserved.
RedAlkemi
Powered by RedAlkemi
Admin Login
Top
